

PROFILE

As a highly motivated and skilled Mobile Developer with near 2 years of expertise in utilizing Flutter. I am eager to take on Junior - Middle Mobile role where I can further enhance my knowledge, develop my technical skills, and work collaboratively with a team of professionals. My passion for learning new languages and technologies, combined with my strong work ethic, make me an ideal candidate for this position.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0348098023

PORTFOLIO: nguyenduonganhhuy

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/ngduonganhhuy/

EMAIL:

ngduonganhhuy@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English - Reading, Listening

EDUCATION

From 08/2018 – 05/2022 **Saigon Technology University** Recent GPA: 3.4 – 3.44

NGUYEN DUONG ANH HUY

WORK EXPERIENCE

Exnodes (Exnodes.vn) Mobile Developer

September 2021 – September 2022

- Develop app according to designer's mockup on Figma, complete user-story according to BA's arrangement and manage time to complete task on JIRA.
- Source Code Management and learning more about DevOps with AWS amazon (CodeCommit), handle image with s3 Bucket
- Coding UI/UX, integration API with Flutter, GETX, JWT, Bloc,....
- Configuration for building app on Android and IOS

GMO Runsystem (Runsystem.net) Mobile Developer

September 2022 - Present

- Define user-story according to BA's arrangement
- Provide solutions to support other members
- Design according to defined user-story, develop app according this design on Adobe XD, Figma
- Configuration for building app on Android and IOS for testing over third application (Testflight, Diawi)
- Deploy app to CHPlay and AppStore

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

- HTML, CSS
- JS
- Dart
- Swift

FRAMEWORKS/PLATFORMS

- React Native (Typescript, Redux)
- Flutter (GetX, Bloc, Riverpod)
- Swift UI, UI Kit
- NodeJS

DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS

- MongoDB
- MySQL
- VERSION CONTROL
 - GIT, Code Commit, Gitlab

PROJECT SHOWCASE

BIZBOOKLY CUSTOMER (2021 – SEP 2022) – Mobile Developer

Description:

 A cutting-edge and user-friendly scheduling application for seamlessly booking appointment at salon, streamlining operations and improving customer experience

Technologies:

- Back-end: Python, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (GetX)

Responsibilities:

- Build a customer app from scratch using flutter
- Configuration HTTP to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM

CH-Play: Bizbookly

BIZBOOKLY STAFF (2021 – SEP 2022) – Mobile Developer

Description:

 An advanced scheduling management app for efficiently organizing and coordinating the schedules of staff members

Technologies:

- Back-end: Python, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (GetX)

Responsibilities:

- Build a customer app from scratch using flutter
- Configuration HTTP to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM

CH-Play: Bizbookly Staff

Yakult Lady (SEP 2022 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

An staff's app for lady to efficiently manage and accomplish their tasks.

Technologies:

- Front-end: AngularJS
- Back-end: Laravel, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (Redux)

Responsibilities:

- Define and design user-flow according file excel from customer on Adobe XD
- Build app from design
- Configuration DIO to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication

- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM
- Deploy app on Testflight, build APK for QC testing
- Creating a promotional campaign for the app.

Yakult Khai Thác (SEP 2022 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

An staff's app for converting from paper processes to app processes for easier task management

Technologies:

- Front-end: AngularJS
- Back-end: Laravel, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (Bloc)

Responsibilities:

- Define and design user-flow according file excel from customer on Adobe XD
- Build app from design
- Configuration DIO to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM
- Deploy app on Testflight, build APK for QC testing

Gonsa Trung Tâm Dược Phẩm (SEP 2022 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

An e-commerce project for buying and selling pharmaceutical products through B2B & B2C

Technologies:

- Front-end: AngularJS
- Back-end: Wordpress, MySQL
- Mobile: Flutter (Bloc)

Responsibilities:

- Build app from design
- Configuration DIO to handle Restful API Integrate JWT to authorization and authentication
- Setup the environment for build app different platforms
- Setup FCM
- Payment with SmartPay
- Deploy app on Testflight, build APK for QC testing
- Deploy app to CHPlay and AppStore

GLOPR Chat App (JUNE 2023 - Present) – Mobile Developer

Description:

A chat app from glopr team

Technologies:

- Front-end: ReactJS
- Back-end: NestJS, MongoDB
- Mobile:
 - o Multi-Platform: Flutter
 - o Single-Platform: Kotlin, Swift

Responsibilities:

- Build app from design
- Deploy app to CHPlay and AppStore

Kibiaccessories (Graduation Project)

Description:

■ Ecommerce – accessories store

Technologies:

- Front-end: React & Redux, ES6, AntD Client, MUI Admin
- Back-end: NodeJS (Express), MongoDB

Responsibilities:

- Build a Back-end server using ExpressJS & Mongoose
- Build a web app for customer using React, Redux & AntDUpload images with firebase storage

- Config Axios to handle Restful API
 Integrate login with Google, Facebook payment with Momo, Stripe API